theaterseatstore.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Theaterseatstore.com, its affiliated websites and our mobile app (collectively, the "Site"). Theaterseatstore, LLC and our branded stores ("Theaterseatstore", "we", "us" or "our") know that you ("you", "your", "yourself") care about how we collect, use, store and share your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"), such as your name, email address, mailing address, ZIP code, phone number and credit card numbers. Theaterseatstore respects your privacy and we want you to enjoy a comfortable and secure shopping experience with us. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use and (under limited circumstances) share your Personal Information ("Privacy Policy").

If you visit our Site, then you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g., message board or chat room), or for the privacy practices of websites that are operated or owned by third parties.

## Here's What We Collect

#### Information you provide to us

We collect, store, and use the Personal Information you voluntarily provide to us. We use this information to provide you with our products and services, to process your transactions, and to improve the quality of our services, as well as for other purposes described in Section III of this Privacy Policy, below.

We may also collect and retain information when you create a gift registry or shopping list or other information you supply to us regarding your personal preferences, likes, and interests, whether it is provided by you directly or through third-party sites that you have authorized to supply such information to us. For example, if you access the Site through a social login functionality (e.g., logging into the Site with your Facebook credentials) or some other site to which you belong, you understand that some content and/or information in your third-party account ("Third Party Account Information") may be transmitted into your account with us if you have authorized your third-party account to make such transmissions. Third Party Account Information transmitted to us is covered by this Privacy Policy. We may also combine information you provide to us with information from public and other reputable sources, including, for example, updated contact information and demographic data.

Please note: You do not need to log in or provide Personal Information to visit our website. However, if you choose not to provide certain information, you may not be able to register with us or take advantage of some or all of our Site features and offerings. Providing us with Personal Information may allow you to receive, among other things, streamlined service, special discounts, faster checkout, order history information, and, if available, other products, information, and/or services you may request.

#### Information we collect automatically

When you visit our Site, we automatically receive and store information about your visit on our servers. Our servers log your IP address, your page requests at our Site, and other information collected from "cookies". A cookie is a small file that is sent to your computer's browser or your mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies remain on your computer or device until they are deleted and tell us, for example, how you arrived at our Site (including search engines and search terms), how you navigate around our Site (including what products you search for and browse), and what products you purchase. We also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and ordering history, and to serve direct personalized marketing from Theaterseatstore (including on other web sites). To opt out of this marketing from Theaterseatstore, contact us directly. In such ways, cookies allow us to provide you with a better and more personalized shopping experience and enable us to make you aware of our products and promotions that may be of interest to you. As explained in Section V of this Privacy Policy, most browsers allow you to block or reject cookies, although this may impact your ability to use features of our Site, including the shopping cart. Theaterseatstore may combine information collected via cookies with Personal Information provided by you.

Along with cookies, we may deliver "web beacons" through our Site and/or e-mails to you which are associated with third-party advertising networks. Web beacons (also called "pixel tags") are small graphic images that may not be visible to Site visitors that collect information about the usage of the Site on an anonymous basis. We may use web beacons in emails to determine device-type and learn if emails have been delivered and opened. Theaterseatstore may also combine information from web beacons with Personal Information provided by you.

Web beacons also allow advertising networks to serve you Theaterseatstore advertisements when you visit other websites. For example, a web beacon logs the products you view at our Site, and then shows you an ad for similar products from Theaterseatstore when you browse to another website. Because your web browser receives advertising from the advertising network's servers, these companies may set, view, or edit their own cookies or web beacons. Many advertising networks participate in the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). The NAI is a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards, and NAI member networks may allow you to opt-out of the cookies or web beacons they deliver. Please note that we do not control the policies of any third parties, including the privacy policies of advertising networks.

If you download or use apps created by us or our partners onto your mobile device, we may also receive information about your location and your device, including the unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. We may also link mobile users' unique IDs or their geographic data to existing customer profiles.

## E-Mails We Send

If you place an order, create an account with us, or otherwise provide us your e-mail address, we may use that e-mail address to confirm your order, confirm the creation of an account, or to notify you of important information or changes to your account or our policies and practices.

In addition, we (or one of our affiliated stores/websites) may send you information about special offers, new products and services, system changes, and other information we think may be of interest to you. We own multiple brands/stores, and if you sign up with one brand/store, you are automatically subscribed to all the others and may receive emails from any of our brands. If you do not wish to receive these e- mails, you may "opt-out" or "unsubscribe" from these e-mails by following the instructions contained in the e-mail. You may also opt-out of receiving these e-mails during the ordering or registration process.

Our Site includes "e-mail to a friend" functionality that allows you to easily share product or other valuable information with your friends and family. Any e-mail addresses provided to us in the use of these features are used solely for the intended purpose of the e-mail communication you authorize. We do not retain these e-mail addresses in our database.

## How We Share Your Personal Information

We may share some of your Personal Information with select companies to facilitate fulfillment of your order and for other purposes identified in this Privacy Policy. With respect to order fulfillment, we share some of your Personal Information with certain intermediaries to accept, process, and ship your order, but only the Personal Information needed for that intermediary to fulfill its obligation to you. For example, our freight carriers and shipping companies are provided with your name and shipping address to deliver your purchased products.

We may also share some of your Personal Information with select companies for purposes of helping introduce you to new resources, services and products compatible with your interests and needs. Information sharing also helps us to guard against potential fraud and other wrongdoing. To facilitate this important effort, Theaterseatstore may partner with select outside companies to enhance our ability to ensure that fraudulent orders do not interfere with our ability to provide you services and products.

Other examples of when we may share Personal Information include:

  * to provide services (e.g., gift registry) that you have requested;
  * at your direction or request (e.g., if you create a gift registry or shopping list and elect to make it available to the public, your information may be accessible on our website, and mobile or social applications);
  * when we believe in good faith that it is necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or to comply with law;
  * when we believe in good faith that it is necessary to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * when we believe, it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * if Theaterseatstore is acquired by or merged with another organization, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party;
  * with our affiliated brands and stores (unless you have opted out of our doing so).

We may also provide certain information, to our partners, including anonymized information and Personal Information to our partners, including, for example, our marketing, testing, personalization and analytics partners. Our partners help us better understand how often and in what ways people use our Site, so that we, and our partners, can provide you with the best experience. For example, we may place a cookie on your browser or mobile device that records the products you viewed at our Site, and then provide that information to a third-party partner, to allow such partner to show you ads for similar products that are available from us.

## Security of Your Personal Information

Theaterseatstore is committed to online data security, and for that reason we take steps to make all information received from you online as secure as reasonably possible from unauthorized access and use that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Our secure server software uses Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption technology to secure your information during transmission.

Your account is protected by a password. If you access your account via a social login, you may have additional or different sign-on protection through that third party (e.g., Facebook, Pinterest, etc.). You are responsible for preventing unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information through your computer or other devices. Do not share your password with anyone and do limit access to your computer or other devices by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

## You've Got Choices

While the Site does not respond to a web browser's "Do Not Track" signal, Theaterseatstore offers its customers choices regarding its use and disclosure of Personal Information. These options include opting out of online behavioral advertising provided by Theaterseatstore or from our third-party marketing partner(s), or choosing for us not to share Personal Information with third parties.

Of course, you are always free to not disclose information to us. In addition, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete cookies as soon as you leave our Site. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, by changing the add-on's settings, or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Although you are not required to accept cookies or provide us information when you visit our sites, if you set your browser to reject cookies (or decide not to provide us certain information) you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this Site.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. If you follow a link to another site, you should read that site's privacy policy. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of the external site company, its website or websites, or the products or services it promotes or sells. When you leave our Site to visit one of these linked sites, the only information transferred to the third party is the fact that you came from our Site.

Theaterseatstore is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of these third-party websites. You should consult the privacy policies at these websites to determine how your information may be collected, stored and used.

## Children's Privacy

Our Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

## You Can "Opt Out" and/or Correct Your Personal Information

Upon your request, we will:

  * correct or update your Personal Information;
  * stop sending emails to your email address or catalogs or other mailings to your physical address; and/or
  * disable your account to prevent future purchases through that account.

Please do not email us your credit-card number or other sensitive personal information.

## We May Change This Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to review it periodically. Our use of information, including Personal Information, is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we collect, store or use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or contacting you directly via e-mail or other means. Your continued use of our Site after any such change constitutes your agreement to any revised terms.

## Effective Date:

November 5, 2016
